Coordonnées

www.linkedin.com/in/cyrille-de-salins-b458b7144 (LinkedIn)

Principales compétences

Maritime Law
Insurance Law
International Trade Law

Languages

Spanish (Professional Working)
English (Full Professional)
French (Native or Bilingual)
Danish (Elementary)

Certifications

Certificate of Professional Competence as Freight Forwarder ('Commissionnaire de Transport') (France)

Publications

Fumigation of dry bulk cargoes : risks and liabilities in charterparties

French and English regimes of the guarantee for latent defects in shipbuilding and repairing

Cyrille de Salins

Senior Legal Counsel - Maritime - at Siemens Gamesa Copenhague, Région de la Capitale, Danemark

Résumé

I am a dual-qualified lawyer, admitted in France and England & Wales, and a Senior Legal Counsel at Siemens Gamesa Renewable Energy A/S.

I specialise in and have extensive experience in relation to the shipping, trade, energy/offshore and insurance industries, from advisory work to dispute resolution.

Expérience

Siemens Gamesa Senior Legal Counsel - Maritime février 2021 - Present (2 ans 5 mois) Veile, South Denmark, Denmark

stream

Managing Associate juin 2019 - janvier 2021 (1 an 8 mois) Paris Area. France

Université de Rouen University Lecturer décembre 2019 - décembre 2019 (1 mois) Rouen Area, France

,

Transport Insurance

Ince & Co 8 ans 10 mois

Managing Associate mai 2018 - juin 2019 (1 an 2 mois)

Paris Area, France

Senior Associate mai 2016 - avril 2018 (2 ans) Région de Paris, France

Associate

septembre 2010 - avril 2016 (5 ans 8 mois)

Paris

Ecole de Management de Normandie

Lecturer

mars 2019 - mars 2019 (1 mois)

Le Havre, Haute-Normandie, France

Contract and Corporate Law (Common Law)

Gard AS

Lawyer on secondment

juillet 2014 - septembre 2014 (3 mois)

Arendal, Aust-Agder County, Norway

Full time secondement to the Dry Cargo South Team

Ince & Co

Trainee

janvier 2010 - juillet 2010 (7 mois)

Paris Area, France

Armateurs de France

Trainee

avril 2009 - mai 2009 (2 mois)

Paris Area, France

French Shipowners' Association

CMS Bureau Francis Lefebvre

Trainee

avril 2008 - juin 2008 (3 mois)

Paris Area, France

Formation

Instituto Marítimo Español

Curso de Trading y Shipping de Crudo y Gas, Oil and Gas · (2019 - 2019)

EFB

CAPA, Law · (2009 - 2010)

Bond University

LLM, International Legal Practice · (2009 - 2009)

Université Paris Dauphine

Master 221 · (2008 - 2009)

Université Panthéon Assas (Paris II)

Master I, Business and Tax Law · (2004 - 2008)

Activité

06/02/2023, Jakob Torring a ajouté un candidat à General Legal Counsel in Copenhagen Area